{
  "title": "Mobile telecommunication expressions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "You can receive, display, edit and/or send text messages on any network that has a ........ agreement.",
      "answers": [
        "multimedia messaging service",
        "roaming",
        "short message service",
        "mailbox"
      ],
      "correct": "roaming"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "It is......... for drivers to exercise proper control of their vehicle at all times whilst using the mobile phone.",
      "answers": ["irrelevant", "illegal", "imperative", "inconsequential"],
      "correct": "imperative"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Before removing the battery from your phone, please ensure that the device is switched off and the ........ is disconnected from the handset.",
      "answers": ["charger", "antenna", "ear piece", "infrared port"],
      "correct": "charger"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "You can transfer data between two cellular phones by using the ........ connection located on the front of your",
      "answers": ["hands free", "main", "infra red", "charger"],
      "correct": "infra red"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Recently ........ phone numbers, answered calls and missed calls are stored in the call log.",
      "answers": ["deleted", "added", "fixed", "dialed"],
      "correct": "dialed"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Before Internet services can be accessed on your cellular phone, you need to ........ to your network operator to enable the relevant configuration information.",
      "answers": [
        "subscribe",
        "contact",
        "get in touch with",
        "make contact with"
      ],
      "correct": "subscribe"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Cell broadcasts allow users to ........ messages on specified topics, such as traffic, and weather information from their network operator.",
      "answers": ["receive", "dispatch", "process", "translate"],
      "correct": "receive"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The message centre number for your network ........ should be preprogrammed on your SIM card.",
      "answers": ["contributor", "supplier", "contractor", "provider"],
      "correct": "provider"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "When you receive an MMS message on your phone, the message ........ is displayed along with a tone, illumination and/or vibration.",
      "answers": ["box", "icon", "key", "connector"],
      "correct": "icon"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Some hand phones are designed to be ........ with certain multimedia messaging services.",
      "answers": ["communicable", "comfortable", "comparable", "compatible"],
      "correct": "compatible"
    }
  ]
}
